High quality wooden kitchen spatula for non-stick pans

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Zeawin Product Landing Page</title>
    <link>https://shop.zeawin.com/spatula</link>
    <description>This is a product feed for Zeawin's Etsy shop.</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>SP200</g:id>
      <g:title>Good Quality Wooden Spatula Set – Non-Toxic, Eco-Friendly, Cooking Utensils for Non-Stick Cookware</g:title>
      <g:description>
        Handrafted from 100% natural wood for a safe, eco-friendly cooking experience. Designed to protect your non-stick cookware, these heat-resistant spatulas are perfect for flipping, stirring, and serving. Non-toxic, plastic-free, and gentle on non-stick surfaces, these spatulas are a must-have for eco-conscious cooks. Ideal for left-handed users and perfect for gifting.
      </g:description>
      <g:link>https://shop.zeawin.com/spatula</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://i.etsystatic.com/28551128/r/il/b01901/5526906862/il_fullxfull.5526906862_7epm.jpg</g:image_link>
      <g:condition>new</g:condition>
      <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
      <g:price>29.40 USD</g:price>
      <g:brand>Zeawin</g:brand>
      <g:mpn>SPWARE-001</g:mpn>
      <g:shipping>
        <g:country>US</g:country>
        <g:service>Standard</g:service>
        <g:price>0.00 USD</g:price>
      </g:shipping>
      <g:product_type>Home & Garden > Kitchen & Dining > Kitchen Tools & Utensils > Cooking Utensils > Spatulas</g:product_type>
      <g:google_product_category>Home & Garden > Kitchen & Dining > Kitchen Tools & Utensils > Cooking Utensils > Spatulas</g:google_product_category>
      <g:identifier_exists>FALSE</g:identifier_exists>
      <g:material>wood</g:material>
      <g:feature>Non-Toxic & Eco-Friendly</g:feature>
      <g:feature>Gentle on Non-Stick Cookware</g:feature>
      <g:feature>Heat-Resistant & Durable</g:feature>
      <g:feature>Versatile Design for All Cooking Needs</g:feature>
      <g:feature>Ergonomic & Comfortable Grip</g:feature>
      <g:keywords>wooden cooking spatula, best wooden spatula, wooden spatula spoon, wooden wok spatula, wooden pizza spatula, wooden turner spatula, slotted wooden spatula, wooden spatula set, left handed wooden spatula, good quality wooden spatula, non-toxic cooking utensils, plastic free spatula, non-toxic kitchen utensils, heat resistant spatula, cooking utensils for non stick cookware, nonstick cookware utensils, spatula turner, are wooden cooking utensils safe</g:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
